[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film St. Elmos Fire, Wendy tells Billy that she made what type of sandwich on her first night living alone?", "correct_answer": "Peanut butter and jelly", "incorrect_answers": ["Ham and cheese", "Turkey", "Tuna"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of structure do tulips grow out from?", "correct_answer": "Bulb", "incorrect_answers": ["Rhizome", "Root", "Tuber"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What legendary Hollywood actress portrayed Lady Marian in the 1976 movie Robin and Marian, starring Sean Connery as Robin Hood?", "correct_answer": "Audrey Hepburn", "incorrect_answers": ["Katharine Hepburn", "Greta Garbo", "Grace Kelly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is considered that Chinese astrology emerged around this time.", "correct_answer": "3000 BC", "incorrect_answers": ["2000 AD", "1000 BC", "5000 BC"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these pairs of a model and a Calvin Klein fragrance, advertised by the model, is correct?", "correct_answer": "Kate Moss - Obsession", "incorrect_answers": ["Kate Moss - Euphoria", "Natalia Vodianova - cK one", "Brooke Shields - Obsession"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Red River College (RRC) is a large and very comprehensive institute of applied learning, located in this city.", "correct_answer": "Winnipeg", "incorrect_answers": ["Ottawa", "Toronto", "Vancouver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This piece of advice: Dont ever let someone tell you, you cant do something. Not even me. is offered in what movie?", "correct_answer": "The Pursuit of Happyness", "incorrect_answers": ["Big Daddy", "Cheaper by the Dozen", "Akeelah and the Bee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1994 Four Weddings and a Funeral Rowan Atkinson had a small but memorable part as this charming inexperienced priest.", "correct_answer": "Father Gerald", "incorrect_answers": ["Reverend George", "Father Thomas", "Reverend Mathew"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is a rumor of a curse surrounding the 1982 movie Poltergeist and its sequels. What happened after the movie was filmed?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["A child actress died at the age of 12.", "One of the actors was brutally murdered.", "An actress was killed at the age of 22."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Prior to fermentation, one of the phases in the production of whisky, dried malt is soaked in water, sugar gets dissolved, and a this sugary liquid is produced.", "correct_answer": "Wort", "incorrect_answers": ["Peat", "Amylase", "Still"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many living species of bears are there?", "correct_answer": "8", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "10", "6"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Reindeer are strict herbivores (vegetarians).", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]